Palestine woke me up. The Palestinian existence as something more than just struggle and one that
is also connected to all of us. The direct correlation between Black people in the United
States and Palestinians who have been killed by state-sanctioned violence. Era of my life where I
am back to being DIY. Like I'm self-publishing my book, What Would the Ancestors Say? The theme of
What Would the Ancestors Say? is that our ancestors are always on call and they're armed and they're
armed with different things but some of them are literally armed with guns to protect us. I went
to LA in 2015 to make it. You're given this thought process that if you scale, if you get out from DIY,
you've made it. If people are investing in something you're doing, they now have opinions, they now have
the ability to take that money back if they don't like your opinion. I can safely say having been in
both spaces that I prefer DIY and I don't want a Zionist name attached to my work. The Zionists
pressured me with continuously canceling my shows. We are watching erasure happen in real time. The
social media accounts of Palestinian journalists after they're assassinated. We have an urgency.
The political education can't happen separate from the spiritual education, which can't happen
separate from the ancestral education. I feel like that is what my work and purpose is to do. And that's
what I think the best of us are doing about Palestine, about Sudan, about the Congo, about the First
Nations, about everybody that has been pushed to the margins.